<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Overcoming poor programming</title>
    <link>https://overcomingpoorprogramming.blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Overcoming poor programming</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://overcomingpoorprogramming.blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blogging from my android phone</title>
      <link>https://overcomingpoorprogramming.blog/post/2021-07-15-blogging-from-my-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://overcomingpoorprogramming.blog/post/2021-07-15-blogging-from-my-phone/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago I published my first proper blog post, and I did it entirely from my android phone. I never once touched another device from the moment I wrote the first word until I brought the post online. This includes drafting the idea, writing and testing code snippets, finishing writing the whole post, previewing it and finally publishing it.
This might not seem special for someone using WordPress or another similar platform but my setup is a little different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audit trail in PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://overcomingpoorprogramming.blog/post/2021-07-13-audit-trail-in-postgresql/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://overcomingpoorprogramming.blog/post/2021-07-13-audit-trail-in-postgresql/</guid>
      <description>6 months or so ago I was building an app that required implementing an audit trail in a PostgreSQL database. At the time I had almost no experience with SQL, so I struggled a bit to find what ended up being quite a simple solution. During this struggle I could not find online almost any resources about what I thought was a common problem, so I&amp;rsquo;ll share what I got.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What this is about</title>
      <link>https://overcomingpoorprogramming.blog/post/2021-02-16-what-this-is-about-and-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://overcomingpoorprogramming.blog/post/2021-02-16-what-this-is-about-and-background/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to take a more organized and methodical approach to my life. Starting a blog seemed a logical path to take, it will force me to organize my thoughts and ideas well enough to write about them, as well as to bring projects to an end so they can be shared with everybody else. Just the fact that this article is online must be a good indication that writing may bring some benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
